<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://timthoughts.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://timthoughts.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Stuff</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/projects/campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/projects/campaign/</guid>
      <description>I love volunteering and assisting in many political campaigns as possible! Nothing like a good old GOTV&amp;hellip;
Since my involvement with the Hillary Clinton campaign ended in November of 2016, I&amp;rsquo;ve come back home to Southern California with a dedicated interest in supporting quality candidates in my local community. I proudly volunteered for Sara Hernandez in the CD 34 race, Frank Yokoyama for his successful bid to the Cerritos City Council, and Mike Fong&amp;rsquo;s bid for the AD51 race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activist Stuff</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/projects/activist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/projects/activist/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished an organizing internship with the Korean Resource Center. It has been an honor to stand among such dedicated and talented activists in the AAPI community to fight for immigration justice against an administration so openly hostile to our communities.
The 2018 elections will be an important checkpoint on the progressive movement&amp;rsquo;s resistance against the Trump administration, but the larger work of organizing towards justice and equality transcend any one election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sanctuary</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/blog/sanctuary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/blog/sanctuary/</guid>
      <description>Huntington Beach, let&amp;rsquo;s do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sanctuary</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/post/sanctuary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/post/sanctuary/</guid>
      <description>Huntington Beach, let&amp;rsquo;s do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recap from 2017!</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/blog/new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 21:49:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/blog/new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
Here&amp;rsquo;s what I did in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switched to Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/blog/new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/blog/new-site/</guid>
      <description>Switched to Hugo because people at #runconf17 were talking about it. LOL
I liked my previous platform on Jekyll + Github Pages, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really posting much on it anyways. I really like using the RStudio tools, consider this a shoutout to my R community.
Thanks to Yihue Xie and Amber Thomas for the blogdown package, (and also for Amber&amp;rsquo;s helpful tutorial), and Vicky Laiio for the Hugo theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal web site! I&amp;rsquo;m Timothy (or just Tim) Phan.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently a political activist and organizer based in Los Angeles and Orange County.
I built this website to archive and document my journey into community organizing. Alternatively, I also enjoy snark-tweeting about Game of Thrones memes if you&amp;rsquo;re into that as well. Season 8, cannot wait&amp;hellip;
Feel free to reach out if you&amp;rsquo;ve got any questions! Ping me if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in progressive politics, Democratic Party stuff in LA/OC, and grassroots activism in my Asian-American community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Job!</title>
      <link>https://timthoughts.com/blog/life-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timthoughts.com/blog/life-update/</guid>
      <description>So much for writing about the election this year. I just moved to Tampa to join Hillary Clinton and the Florida Democrats, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on the data and analytics team for the duration of the election. Volunteering as a fellow during the California primary for HRC will always be a highlight of my life, and I&amp;rsquo;m really thankful for all the great people I met.
But now the hardest part comes next.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>